[EPIC]⚡ This is a national emergency.
[EPIC]⚡ Detonator's charged!
[EPIC]⚡ We're in a race against the Nazis.
[EPIC]⚡ I know what it means if the Nazis have a bomb.
[EPIC]⚡ We have a 12 -month head start.
[EPIC]⚡ 18.
[EPIC]⚡ How could you possibly know that?
[EPIC]⚡ We've got one hope.
[EPIC]⚡ All America's industrial might and scientific innovation connected here.
[EPIC]⚡ Secret laboratory.
[EPIC]⚡ Keep everyone there until it's dark.
[EPIC]⚡ Let's go recruit some scientists.
[EPIC]⚡ Build a town, build it fast.
[EPIC]⚡ We don't let scientists bring their families.
[EPIC]⚡ We'll never get the best.
[EPIC]⚡ Why would we go to the middle of nowhere for who knows
[EPIC]⚡ how long?
[EPIC]⚡ Why?
[EPIC]⚡ How about because this is the most important thing
[EPIC]⚡ to ever happen in the history of the world?
[EPIC]⚡ You're the great improviser, but this you can't do in your head.
[EPIC]⚡ Are we saying there's a chance that when we push that button,
[EPIC]⚡ we destroy the world?
[EPIC]⚡ Chances are near zero.
[EPIC]⚡ Near zero.
[EPIC]⚡ What do you want from theory alone?
[EPIC]⚡ Zero would be nice.
[EPIC]⚡ It's a matter of life and death.
[EPIC]⚡ I can perform this miracle.
[EPIC]⚡ World War II would be over.
[EPIC]⚡ Our boys would come home.
[EPIC]⚡ It's happening, isn't it?
[EPIC]⚡ The world will remember this day.
[EPIC]⚡ Kill.
[EPIC]⚡ We'll ensure a peace mankind has never seen.
[EPIC]⚡ Until somebody builds a bigger bomb.
[CALM]😌 You are the man who gave them the power to destroy themselves
[CALM]😌 and the world is not prepared.
[EPIC]⚡ Truman needs to know what's next.
[EPIC]⚡ What's next?
[EPIC]⚡ One.